atlastravelsonline.com 2019-06-14

# Atlas Travels Online Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

As a registered member of Atlas Travels, you will be entitled to savings and benefits on airfares, hotel reservations, and car rentals, among other travel services. In addition, look forward to receiving monthly newsletters and exclusive promotions offering special deals. That's why we've provided this Privacy Policy, which sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and protection of the personal information of those using the Atlas Travels website. Personal information means information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, telephone number, e - mail address, and credit card number. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy, and become familiar with it, but you should know that we do not sell or rent our customers' personal information to third parties. Please note that we review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. Therefore, you may wish to bookmark this page and/or periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version. Regardless of later updates, we will abide by the privacy practices described to you in this Privacy Policy at the time you provided us with your personal information.

This Privacy Policy explains the following:

## What personal information we collect from you and how we use it?

When browsing our site, you are required to log on with your log in Id and password provided by your administration staff or by staff of Atlas Tours and Travels Pvt Ltd.

Member Profile 

As an Atlas Travels Online site member, administration staff can choose to complete traveler online profile by providing us with travel preferences, frequent - traveler or affinity numbers, credit card billing information and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist you in making reservations quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly. In order to purchase travel and/or related services through our site, user must provide us with personal information such as your name, Payment Method Credit/ Advance Float or credit card number and expiration date, credit card billing address, Date of Birth in case of child, telephone number, e - mail address and the name or names of the person(s) traveling .We may also ask you for other personal information, such as your frequent traveler numbers. We require this information to share with the service providers like airlines, hotels etc to process, fulfill and confirm your reservations and transactions and keep you informed of each transaction's status. If you are making a reservation for one or more travelers other than yourself, you must confirm and represent that each of these other travelers have agreed, in advance, that you may disclose their personal information to us.

Automatic Logging of Session Data 

We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on Atlas Travels website. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the site, how long visitors to the site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

## With whom (if anyone) your personal information is shared? 

When you reserve or purchase travel services through ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD., we must provide certain of your personal information to the airline, hotel, car - rental agency, travel agency or other involved third party to enable the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. However, we do not sell or trade individual customer names or other personal information to third parties without the consent of the user. Atlas uses non - personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Atlas Travels website. Information such as credit card details and net banking details are usually collected directly by the Payment Gateways and Banks and not by Atlas. These details if stored or retained by us are shared only with government/statutory/security agencies to screen for fraudulent activities and with third parties only for the purpose of Cash Back & Discounts, Chargebacks, if applicable.

## What safeguards we have in place to protect your personal information? 

All payments on the atlastravels.com site is Verisign SSL secured. This means all personal information you provide to ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. The same process happens when you make travel purchases on the Atlas Travels site.

## What other information should I know about my privacy? 

Atlas Travels site contains links to other web sites (Ã¢Â?Â?Linked SitesÃ¢Â?Â?). Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another web site for which ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, and your Atlas Travels site membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online. The Linked Sites are not under the control of Atlas and Atlas is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. Atlas is not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by the User from any Linked Site. Atlas is providing these links to the User only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Atlas or the Website of the Linked Sites or any association with its operators or owners including the legal heirs or assigns thereof. Atlas is not responsible for any errors, omissions or representations on any Linked Site. Atlas does not endorse any advertiser on any Linked Site in any manner. The Users are requested to verify the accuracy of all information on their own before undertaking any reliance on such information. In addition to the circumstances described above, ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. may disclose the Atlas Travels site member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition This policy is effective as of January 1st January 2012. Any material changes in the way ATLAS TOURS AND TRAVELS PVT. LTD. uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement.
